https://www.keiabroad.org/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
KEI respects the privacy of users of this web site. This privacy policy has been created to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy and security. It outlines the type of information collected by this website, how the information is used and the choices you have in sharing your information with KEI.
Newsletters & inquiry forms
All users who submit an inquiry to KEI receive an email reply and subscribed to the KEI newsletter. Users can also subscribe to the newsletter by completing the subscription form. You will be asked to provide personal information such as your name and email address. The information you provide will be stored for the sole purpose of sending information to you. The information may be shared only if approved by you or required by law. You may opt out of receiving email updates and newsletter at any time.
Cookies
Cookies are small data files that can be used to collect and store information, such as the type of computer you are using and how often you log on to a site. This web site does not use cookies that are stored permanently on your computer. The use of cookies by this website is solely for the purpose of navigation.
External links
This site contains links to external websites. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this website and not to other websites that you may access from here. KEI is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. Please be aware that when you leave this site, you should read the privacy policies of each and every other website that asks you to provide personal information.
Notification of changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted on this website so that users are always aware of the type of information collected, how it is used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed.
Report website problems...
Name * E-Mail * Subject *
Message *
CHOOSE A PROGRAMCHOOSE A PROGRAMAUSTRALIACHINACOSTA RICAECUADORENGLANDFRANCEINDIAIRELANDITALYJAPANKENYAPERURUSSIASCOTLANDSPAINTHAILANDTURKEYUAECHOOSE A SUBJECTCHOOSE A SUBJECTBUSINESSCOMMUNICATIONSCOMPUTER SCIENCEDESIGN & ARCHITECTUREEDUCATIONENGINEERINGENVIRONMENTFASHIONHOSPITALITYHUMANITIESINTERNATIONAL RELATIONSLANGUAGESLAW & CRIMINOLOGYMEDICINE & HEALTHPERFORMING ARTSPSYCHOLOGYSCIENCESOCIAL SCIENCESPORTSINTERNSHIPSKNOWLEDGE EXCHANGE INSTITUTE
Phone: 1.212.931.9953 | Toll Free: 1.800.831.5095 | Fax: 1.212.528.2095
48 Broadway, Suite 2, Haverstraw, New York, 10927 USA
info@KEIabroad.org | webmaster@KEIabroad.org
©Knowledge Exchange Institute. All rights reserved, worldwide: Terms of Use | Privacy Statement
Scroll to top
